<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<openerp>
<data>

<template id="principal" name="Principal">
    <t t-call="website.layout">
        <span class="hidden" id="active_link">0,3</span>
      <div class="white_panel" id="principals">
          <h1 class="title">PRINCIPALS</h1><br/>
          <ul>
              <li><a class="orange_text_title_small_link bold">Fred Olsen Cruise Lines</a></li>
              <li><a class="orange_text_title_small_link bold">Fred Olsen Crewing and Consultancy Services LTD (FOCCS)</a></li>
              <li><a class="orange_text_title_small_link bold">Yinson Production AS</a></li>
              <li><a class="orange_text_title_small_link bold">Carnival Cruise Lines</a></li>
          </ul>
          <hr/>
          
          <span class="orange_text_title_small">Fred Olsen Cruise Lines</span><br/><br/>
          
          Fred. Olsen Cruises is one of the businesses of the Fred. Olsen family. 
          Based in the UK , Fred. Olsen business interests are varied.<br/><br/>
          
          They include travel and leisure interests (Fred. Olsen Travel Ltd),
          renewable energy (The Natural Power Consultants Ltd) and estate management 
          (Forrest Estate Ltd). UK offices are located principally in London, Ipswich 
          and south of Glasgow in Scotland.<br/><br/>
          
          Fred. Olsen Cruise Lines is located in Ipswich.Fred. Olsen Limited provides 
          management, IT, office facilities and HR support services to these companies.
          To know more about the company, click www.fredolsencruises.co.uk<br/><br/>
          
          
          <span class="orange_text_title_small">Fred Olsen Cruise Lines</span><br/><br/>
          Fred. Olsen Crewing and Consultancy Services Ltd. (FOCCS) provides innovative 
          and tailored services for the transport, installation and maintenance of offshore wind parks. 
          FOCCS can provide all the key elements required for offshore installation in provision of 
          installation jack-ups, crew transfer vessels, skilled installation personnel and turn key solution.
          <br/><br/>
          
          Also, FOCCS offered the Operations and Maintenance phase which is the most critical in the 
          lifetime of an offshore wind park as this phase is greatly affects overall life-cycle cost 
          with an in-house capability to provide you with the necessary services, vessels, 
          crew and service technicians.<br/><br/>
          
          Today, FOCCS is responsible for the daily operation of two (2) self elevating wind turbine 
          installation and crane unit namely Bold Tern and Brave Tern.
          <br/><br/>
          
          <span class="orange_text_title_small">Yinson Production AS</span><br/><br/>
          
          Yinson Production AS is committed to the highest standards with respect to Health, 
          Safety and Environmental Protection and their objective is zero accidents throughout the 
          operations.<br/><br/>
          
          Its vision is to become a preferred long-term partner for oil companies and/or oil field 
          developers through a commitment to quality, adhering to long-term values and seeking 
          continual improvement to the services it provides.<br/><br/>
          
          Maintaining close customer relationships, working cost-efficiently, ensuring, quality 
          through continuous improvement will be, a long-sided safety, highest priority throughout 
          Yinson Production’s operations.<br/><br/>
          
          Yinson Production will manage and control the above through it Management System that 
          complies with the requirements of the international standard EN ISO 9001-2000, determining 
          and setting quality objectives and means for measuring and analyzing the effectiveness 
          of the process and procedures.<br/><br/>
          
          
          <span class="orange_text_title_small">Carnival Cruise Lines</span><br/><br/>
          Carnival is “The World’s Most Popular Cruise Line”, with 25 ships operating 3 to 18 day 
          voyages to The Bahamas, Caribbean, Mexican Riviera, Alaska, Hawaii, Canada, New England 
          and Australia.<br/><br/><br/><br/>
          
          
          
          
      </div>
    </t>
</template>


<template id="aboutus" name="About Us">
    <t t-call="website.layout">
        <span class="hidden" id="active_link">0,1</span>
      
        <div class="white_panel" id="about_us">
          <h1 class="title">ABOUT US</h1><br/>
          
          
          <span class="orange_text_title_small">Bahia Shipping Services, Inc. (BSSI) or simply Bahia</span>
           was registered with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in December 1987 and started 
           deploying Filipino seafarers in January 1988 for then principal, Blackfriars Shipping Co. 
           Ltd. Bahia then provided seafarers for only five vessels, now the company has grown to be one of 
           the leading providers of seafarers for foreign principals and continue to grow to provide 
           employment to most Filipinos.
           <hr/>
          
          
          <span class="orange_text_title">VISION STATEMENT</span><br/><br/>
          
          To provide our Principals with first-rate Filipino seafarers.
          <hr/>
          
          
          <span class="orange_text_title">MISSION STATEMENT</span><br/><br/>
          
          Bahia Shipping Services Inc. is a company committed to recruit and supply STCW certified, 
          competent, disciplined and hardworking Filipino seafarers for our foreign Principals. <br/><br/>
          
          We are committed to uphold the best interest of the Filipino seafarers and to continuously 
          promote the Philippines as a significant source of seafarers in the global labor market.
          <hr/>
          
          
          <span class="orange_text_title">QUALITY POLICY</span><br/><br/>
          
          To provide qualified and well-trained crew as required by our Principals in manning their 
          vessels, and to meet the applicable statutory/regulatory requirements to ensure ship’s operation 
          and protection of the marine environment.
          <hr/>
          
          
          <span class="orange_text_title">OUR CORPORATE VALUES</span><br/><br/>
          
          We at Bahia Shipping Services Inc. were incorporated with a set of core values embodied 
          by the Chairman of the Board and continues to be the standard of its employees.<br/><br/>
          
          <span class="orange_text_title_small">INTEGRITY</span><br/>
          
          <ul>
              <li>We steadily adhere to strict moral and ethical codes in performing our duties and in interaction towards our customers.</li>
          </ul><br/>
          
          
          <span class="orange_text_title_small">LOYALTY</span><br/>
          
          <ul>
              <li>
                    The company duly recognize the valuable contributions of the crewmembers. 
                    They are indeed the greatest assets of the company. We owe to this loyal seafarers the success of the company.
              </li>
          </ul><br/>
          
          
          <span class="orange_text_title_small">SERVICE</span><br/>
          
          <ul>
              <li>
                    MEMBER; Filipino Association for Mariners’ Employment (FAME), the largest 
                    association of manning agencies in the Philippines since 1994.
              </li>
          </ul><br/><hr/>
          
          
          <h2 class="title2 text-center">OPERATIONAL EXCELLENCE</h2>
          
          <img class="img_link" src="website/static/src/img/bahia/poea1.png"/>
          
          
          <div class="text-center bold">
              POEA Top Performer Awardee<br/>
              We are POEA Top Performer Awardee for 2002 and 2006. Given to Bahia for its 
              commendable performance and accomplishments. Two citations were likewise given in recognition to the agency’s 
              promotion and creation of employment opportunities for Filipino seafarers. 
          </div>
          
          
          <img class="img_link" src="website/static/src/img/bahia/iso.png"/>
          
          
          <div class="text-center bold">
              ISO Certified 9001/2008 – Bureau Veritas Quality International (BVQI)<br/>
              We are Bureau Veritas Quality International certified since 2000.<br/><br/>
              We are currently aiming for ISO 9001:2015 trasition in time for our re-Certification
          </div>
          
          
          
          <img class="img_link" src="website/static/src/img/bahia/marlins.png"/>
          
          
          <div class="text-center bold">
              Marlins Approved Test Center)<br/>
              We are an accredited Marlins English Test Center since February 15, 2007.
          </div>
          
          
          <img class="img_link" src="website/static/src/img/bahia/poea2.png"/>
          
          
          <div class="text-center bold">
              In-House Processing of Contract<br/>
              Since 2002, Bahia processed contracts in-house. Giiven as a privilege by POEA 
              due to the volume of seafarers regularly deployed, and as an incentive due to the 
              awards and citations received.
          </div>
          
          
          <img class="img_link" src="website/static/src/img/bahia/pdos.png"/>
          
          
          <div class="text-center bold">
              PDOS Accredited Center<br/>
              Since 2003, Bahia is an accredited PDOS Training Center.
          </div>
          
          
          <img style="width:230px;" class="img_link" src="website/static/src/img/bahia/Logo-SMO-2011.jpg"/>
          
          
          <div class="text-center bold">
              Maritime Labour Convention (MLC) 2006<br/><br/>
              “We have been certified with regard to MLC compliance since August 31, 2012 under Bureau Vertias”
          </div>
          
          
          
          <img style="width:130px;" class="img_link" src="website/static/src/img/bahia/FAME.jpg"/>
          
          
          <div class="text-center bold">
               Filipino Association for Mariners’ Employment Inc. (FAME)<br/><br/>
              Bahia was awarded last March 2015, a “Plaque of Recognition” in grateful  
              appreciation of 20 years of loyal and dedicated membership and affiliation with the 
              Association and for the active commitment, support and adherence to the vision and goals of 
              the Association for the greater prosperity of its members in particular and the Philippine 
              Seafaring and Maritime Industry in general.

          </div>
          
          <hr/>
          
          
          
          
        </div>
    </t>
</template>




<template id="contactus" name="Contact Us">
    <t t-call="website.layout">
         <span class="hidden" id="active_link">0,5</span>
        <div class="white_panel" id="contact_us">
            <h1 class="title">CONTACT US</h1>
            <ul>
                <li>Monday – Friday</li>
                <li>7:00am – 4:00pm</li>
                <li>Telephone Nos :   +632 5217456   /   +632 5260691</li>
                <li>Fax No. :  +632 5217538</li>
            </ul>
            <hr/>
        </div>
    </t>
</template>


<template id="homepage" name="Home Page">
    <t t-call="website.layout">
        <span class="hidden" id="active_link">0,0</span>
      
        <div class="white_panel" id="home">
          <h1 class="title">HOME</h1><br/>
          
          <h2 class="title2 text-center">Welcome to Bahia Shipping Services Inc.</h2>
          
          <img src="/website/static/src/img/bahia/Bahia-Group.jpg"/>
          
          <h3 class="text-center">
                We recruit and deploy Filipino seafarers for Cruise Vessels, Off-Shore 
                vessels and Self Elevating Wind Turbine Installation and Crane Unit
          </h3><br/>
          
          <h3 class="text-center">
              Our foreign principals are Fred Olsen Cruise Lines, Yinson Production AS, 
              Carnival Cruise Lines and  Fred Olsen Crewing and Consultancy LTD
          </h3>
          
          
        </div>
    </t>
</template>




<template id="faqs" name="FAQS">
    <t t-call="website.layout">
        <span class="hidden" id="active_link">1,0</span>
        <div class="white_panel" id="faqs">
            <h1 class="title">FAQs</h1>
            <ul>
                <li><a class="orange_text_title_small_link bold"> >> RECRUITMENT</a></li><br/>
                <li><a class="orange_text_title_small_link bold"> >> CREWING </a></li><br/>
                <li><a class="orange_text_title_small_link bold"> >> ALLOTMENT AND DEDUCTIONS</a></li><br/>
            </ul>
            
            <hr/>
            
            <span class="orange_text_title_small_link bold"> >> RECRUITMENT</span>
            
            What is a seafarer and how to be employed as such?<br/><br/>
            
            By definition, a seafarer is one who earns his/her living by service at 
            sea. To be employed as such, the person should have the necessary skills 
            and documents corresponding to the position available on board.<br/><br/>
            
            To know more about the Careers offered by our Principals, please click 
            <a href="http://www.bahiashipping.ph/careers.php" class="orange_text_title_small_link">Careers Menu</a>
            <br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">What are the required documents to be a seafarer?</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            Generally speaking, those would be seafarers must possess the following documents <br/><br/>
            
            <ul>
                <li>Certificate(s) of work employment</li><br/>
                <li>Valid Seaman’s Book or (SIRB)</li><br/>
                <li>Valid Passport</li><br/>
                <li>Valid Basic Training Certificate</li><br/>
                <li>Certificate(s) of work related training(s)</li><br/>
            </ul>
            
            To know how to acquire such documents, please refer to the General Guidelines<br/><br/>
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">I have the above documents, is it enough for me to get hired by your company?</span><br/><br/>
            
            No, additional requirements are based on the position applied, please see 
            the Careers Menu for explanation on the different position requirements.<br/><br/>
            
            However, the minimum requirements for all positions in addition to the 
            documents mentioned above, are the following:<br/><br/>
            
            <ul>
                <li>Must be able to confidently communicate in English</li><br/>
                <li>Height requirement of at least 5’5″ for Males</li><br/>
                <li>Height requirement of at least 5’3″ for Females</li><br/>
                <li>
                        Has at least 12 months of recent employment gained from an international or 
                        local vessel or extensive land-based experience gained from a reputable establishment.
                </li><br/>
            </ul>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;"><br/>How to apply in your Company?</span><br/><br/>
            
            You may send us your application by visiting our website at www.bahiashipping.ph and click <a class="orange_text_title_small_link">Apply Now.</a><br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:16px;color:gray !important;">WE DO NOT ENTERTAIN WALK-IN APPLICANTS.</span><br/><br/>
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">When and where can I follow-up my application?</span><br/><br/>
            
            Once your application passed the initial assessment, kindly expect a response from us for the status of your application.<br/><br/>
            
            <span style="font-size:16px;color:gray !important;">WE DO NOT ENTERTAIN PERSONAL FOLLOW-UPS.</span><br/><br/>
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">I am a referral by one of your seafarers, am I assured of an employment onboard by your company?</span><br/><br/>
            
            No, although referrals are given priority by the company, still referrals need to comply with the minimum requirements.<br/><br/>
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">Do you charge placement fee?</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:16px;color:gray !important;">ABSOLUTELY, NO PLACEMENT FEE IS TO BE COLLECTED.</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            <span class="orange_text_title_small_link bold"> >> RECRUITMENT</span><br/><br/>
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">What is the contract duration of your seafarers?</span><br/><br/>
            
            The contract duration of our seafarers depend on what Principal they are employed, 
            however the usual duration is up to 10 months.<br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">What is your procedure regarding rejoining crew?</span><br/><br/>
            
            Crew rotation of seafarers belonging to principals, Fred Olsen Cruise Lines, Carnival Cruise Lines, Fred Olsen Crewing and Consultancy LTD, 
            Yinson Production AS and Fred Olsen Marine Services are handled by their respective principals, vacation is usually minimum of two months.
            <br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">I’m an ex-crew of your company and I wish to re-apply, can I do so?</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            Yes, you may contact your respective Crewing Managers.<br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">I am a current crew of one of your Principals, and I want to apply to other Principals within the company, can I do so?</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            Yes, you may apply from one Principal to another. Submit your comprehensive resume and a copy of your last performance appraisal to Recruitment 
            Coordinator. However, transfer is not guaranteed and employment is based on vacancy and Principal’s approval.<br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">What are the positions deployed by your Company?</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            The positions supplied by Bahia differs from one principal to another, to know more, please click Careers Menu.<br/><br/>
        </div>
    </t>
</template>


<template id="generalguidelines" name="GENERALGUIDELINES">
    <t t-call="website.layout">
        <span class="hidden" id="active_link">1,1</span>
        <div class="white_panel" id="generalguidelines">
            <h1 class="title">General Guidelines</h1>

            <span style="font-size:17px;">Where and how do I get an NBI clearance?</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            The NBI clearance that you must have is for Visa – Seaman. You can apply at the NBI Clearance 
            Center (Victory Central Mall #717 Old Victory Liner Cmpd. Rizal Ave., Monumento, 
            Caloocan City or at any NBI Satellite Offices, NBI Regional / District Offices and 
            NBI Kiosk nationwide.For a detailed procedure on how to obtain the certificate and 
            the fees to be collected, please see <a href="http://www.nbi.gov.ph/">NBI website</a>.<br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">Where do I get a copy of my birth certificate?</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            Birth Certificates are requested from The Office of the Civil Registrar General of the National 
            Statistics Office. You may apply personally or for your convenience, NSO is accepting online 
            applications, payments can also be made thru banks.For more details, you can login to their 
            website at <a href="http://www.e-census.com.ph"> http://www.e-census.com.ph</a><br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">How can I get an SSS ID?</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            Every seafarer must have a Social Security System (SSS) ID as required by the Philippine Government. 
            For more information on where to apply, the requirements and the forms to be 
            filled-up, please log on to their website at <a href=" http://www.sss.gov.ph">  http://www.sss.gov.ph</a><br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">What is CAV? And where can I get it?</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            For College graduates, you can secure your CAV or Certificate of Authentication and Verification 
            from the CHED office NCR or to the CHED office in the provinces, depending on where your school is 
            located, please see their website at <a href="http://www.ched.gov.ph/services/students/cav.html">http://www.ched.gov.ph/services/students/cav.html</a>. For 
            High School Graduates, you can secure your CAV from DECS NCR – (located at the back of SM City – 
            Annex, Quezon City or from any DECS offices in the provinces depending on where your school is located<br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">Where and how do I apply for a Passport?</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            Application for passport is now online.Applicants may set an appointment by going on 
            line <a href="http://www.dfa.gov.ph/main/index.php/consular-services/passport">
            http://www.dfa.gov.ph/main/index.php/consular-services/passport</a> or by calling 
            737-1000.Applicants are no longer required to bring photographs since they will have 
            their picture taken using ePassport data capturing machines at DFA-OCA. OCA building is 
            located at the corner of Macapagal Avenue and Bradco Street, Aseana Business Park.E-passport 
            can be obtained through the different consular offices nationawide, click 
            <a href="http://www.dfa.gov.ph/main/index.php/about-the-dfa/rp-embassies-consulates-a-rcos/regional-consular-offices">
                http://www.dfa.gov.ph/main/index.php/about-the-dfa/rp-embassies-consulates-a-rcos/regional-consular-offices
            </a>.<br/><br/>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">What is Basic Safety Course? Where can I take this course get the course?</span><br/><br/>
            
            
            Individuals who wish to pursue a career in seafaring should complete a Basic Safety Course (BSC) 
            training obtained from an accredited maritime training center duly approved by the Maritime Training 
            Council, a division of the Philippine Overseas Employment Agency.The course covers the mandatory minimum 
            requirements prescribed in Regulation VI/1, and Section A-VI/1 of STCW’95. The training lasts for one 
            week lecture and one day actual training. It covers the following subjects:<br/><br/>
            
            
            <ul>
                <li>Elementary First Aid</li><br/>
                <li>Personal Survival Techniques</li><br/>
                <li>Fire Prevention and Fire Fighting</li><br/>
                <li>Personal Safety and Social Responsibility</li><br/>
                <li>Medical Emergency</li><br/>
                <li>First Aid</li><br/>
            </ul>
            
            For a list of accredited training centers, log on to <a href="http://www.mtc.gov.ph"> http://www.mtc.gov.ph</a><br/><br/>
            
            
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">What are the requirements to secure a Seaman’s Book (Seafarer’s identification and Record Book) for new applicants?</span><br/><br/>
            
            <ul>
                <li>Transcript of Record (High School TOR for High School Graduates) (College TOR for College Graduates)</li><br/>
                <li>School Diploma (High School Diploma for High School Graduates ) (College Diploma for College Graduates)</li><br/>
                <li>Certificate of Authentication and Verification (CAV)</li><br/>
                <li>Certified True Copy of Birth Certificate</li><br/>
                <li>NBI Clearance – visa seaman</li><br/>
                <li>2 pcs Passport size colored picture with white background</li><br/>
                <li>Basic Safety Course Certificate</li><br/>
            </ul>
            
            
            <span style="font-size:17px;">Where do I apply for a Seaman’s Book?</span><br/><br/>
            
            File your application together with the above requirements at the Maritime Industry 
            Authority (MARINA), located at Parkview Plaza, Kalaw cor Taft Ave, Manila.To know more about 
            the requirements and procedures, you may login to their website at 
            <a href="http://www.marina.gov.ph/faqs/default.aspx">http://www.marina.gov.ph/faqs/default.aspx</a><br/><br/>
        </div>
    </t>
</template>


<template id="announcements" name="Announcements">
    <t t-call="website.layout">
        <span class="hidden" id="active_link">1,2</span>
        <div class="white_panel" id="announcements">
            <h1 class="title">Announcements</h1>
        </div>
    </t>
</template>


<template id="gallery" name="Gallery">
    <t t-call="website.layout">
        <span class="hidden" id="active_link">1,3</span>
        <div class="white_panel" id="gallery">
            <h1 class="title">Gallery</h1>


            <div id="myCarousel" class="carousel slide" data-ride="carousel">
                  <!-- Indicators -->
                  <ol class="carousel-indicators">
                    <li data-target="#myCarousel" data-slide-to="0" class="active"></li>
                    <li data-target="#myCarousel" data-slide-to="1"></li>
                    <li data-target="#myCarousel" data-slide-to="2"></li>
                    <li data-target="#myCarousel" data-slide-to="3"></li>
                  </ol>
                
                  <!-- Wrapper for slides -->
                  <div class="carousel-inner" role="listbox">
                    <div class="item active">
                      <img src="/website/static/src/img/bahia/img1.jpg" alt="Chania" />
                    </div>
                
                    <div class="item">
                      <img src="/website/static/src/img/bahia/img2.jpg" alt="Chania" />
                    </div>
                
                    <div class="item">
                      <img src="/website/static/src/img/bahia/img3.jpg" alt="Flower" />
                    </div>
                
                    <div class="item">
                      <img src="/website/static/src/img/bahia/img4.jpg" alt="Flower" />
                    </div>
                    
                    <div class="item">
                      <img src="/website/static/src/img/bahia/img5.jpg" alt="Flower" />
                    </div>
                  </div>
                
                  <!-- Left and right controls -->
                  <a class="left carousel-control" href="#myCarousel" role="button" data-slide="prev">
                    <span class="glyphicon glyphicon-chevron-left" aria-hidden="true"></span>
                    <span class="sr-only">Previous</span>
                  </a>
                  <a class="right carousel-control" href="#myCarousel" role="button" data-slide="next">
                    <span class="glyphicon glyphicon-chevron-right" aria-hidden="true"></span>
                    <span class="sr-only">Next</span>
                  </a>
                </div>
        </div>
    </t>
</template>


<template id="governmentlinks" name="GOVERNMENTLINKS">
    <t t-call="website.layout">
        <span class="hidden" id="active_link">1,4</span>
        <div class="white_panel" id="governmentlinks">
            <h1 class="title">Government Links</h1>

            <a href="http://marina.gov.ph/">Maritime Industry Authority</a><br/><br/>
            
            <a href="http://www.poea.gov.ph/">Philippine Overseas Employment Administration</a><br/><br/>
            
            <a href="http://www.pagibigfund.gov.ph/">Home Development Mutual Fund (“PAGIBIG”)</a><br/><br/>
            
            <a href="http://www.sss.gov.ph/">Social Security System (“SSS”)</a><br/><br/>
            
            <a href="http://www.nbi.gov.ph/">National Bureau of Investigation (“NBI”)</a><br/><br/>
            
            <a href="http://maps.nationalgeographic.com/maps">National Geographic Maps</a><br/><br/>
            
            <a href="http://www.tesda.gov.ph/">Technical Education and Skills Development Authority (TESDA)</a><br/><br/>
            
            <span>o  TESDA online program</span><br/><br/>
            
            <span>o  List of assessment centers</span><br/><br/>
            
            <span>o  CAV</span><br/><br/>
            
            <a href="http://www.owwa.gov.ph/">Overseas Workers Welfare Administration (OWWA)</a><br/><br/>
            
            <a href="http://www.owwa.gov.ph/?q=content/programs-services">o Programs and services</a><br/><br/>
            
            <a href="http://www.owwa.gov.ph/?q=content/downloads-0">o Form downloads</a><br/><br/>
            
            <a href="http://www.philhealth.gov.ph/">PhilHealth</a><br/><br/>
            
            <span>o  Forms downloads</span><br/><br/>
            
            <span>o  Online services</span><br/><br/>
        </div>
    </t>
</template>











</data>
</openerp>
